{
    "id": "278f2ceac8c84f5dbecddcd1c7973fcc",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "No sooner had I seen the huge boulder lying in the middle of the road, ………………….. I stopped the car.",
            "description": "Sooner is a comparative word use than after it.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b32e8c74b0bd4047b8078e892dfc872e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is high time we ………………….. the police.",
            "description": "After it is high time, we use a past tense with a present meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "called",
                "have called",
                "call"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aeac3355190345c8af41f84a9c8a4c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the feminine gender of fox?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "foxen",
                "vixen",
                "foxine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d6cb4fb2ee240908d2cb19028401bb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A little",
                "Little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67e0fa7387e546f8bf60d510e8da618e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. is the best form of flattery.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Imitation",
                "Copying",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32129a477f4544308c02dd7bfa2e8d7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told him a story. Identify the direct object.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "story"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c7bcdc0a90e453784a464c47f520798"
        },
        {
            "question": "He showed me his possessions. Identify the indirect object.",
            "description": "The indirect object is the person who receives something.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "his",
                "possessions"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5284678d1c5d49be82315357b4ec6bc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the wheels of the car ……………………… punctured.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular expression one. ",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e80e53d7b59425e9290df9bb31dd6b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The spider was busy …………………….. web.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "making",
                "weaving",
                "spinning"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e300836799ab4ca4aae6699e202a81b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "A shoal of …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cows",
                "fish",
                "monkeys"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "803341e82d97409b8f89dafad06f375c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He drives very carefully. Here very is an ……………………",
            "description": "Very modifies the adjective carefully. Only an adverb can modify an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54942df4b6c0452494483372396b3042"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I visited him yesterday, he ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slept",
                "was sleeping",
                "is sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "781d28fbd42c4b6283efad9e38d526ca"
        }
    ]
}